freedownloadsplace.com 2019-04-27

# Privacy and Cookie Policy - Soft Famous

Privacy and Cookie Policy

Please read this Privacy policy carefully. Is available using our site.  
For any further information, we can be contacted via e-mail (see the link Contact us)

 **Collection of Information about your personal data or information**  
During you are surfing our site, we collect personally identifiable information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc. and information about your computer details like IP, browser, operating system, country, the speed of the Internet. Some of these data are voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. The information you provide to us is not used in another manner that is described in the contact forms. Navigating these pages you can use all information just for personal use, not for commercial one.

 **Types of Data collected**

  * we collect the IP of the user to make statistics by country. We delete the data after 60 days.

## Cookie and Tracking Technology

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and [content network privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

The softfamous.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered.It doesn’t matter if you are getting a product or not. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

[Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/) is using cookies to collect data from your computer. Reading this page you automatically agree with these cookies.

We may use [third-party advertising companies](http://dh0xkipwqhwym.cloudfront.net/pp.html) to serve ads when you visit our website.

This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymized tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at [the About Cookies website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers.

For any further information, you can contact us using email communication [here](https://softfamous.com/contact/).
